The fight for justice is the greatest battle of all time.
Justice Society: World War II is a animation, war, science
fiction film directed by Jeff Wamester.
When the Flash finds himself dropped into the middle of World War II, he joins forces with
Wonder Woman and her top-secret team known as the Justice Society of America.
Flash (voice), played by Matt Bomer.
Wonder Woman (voice), played by Stana Katic.
Hawkman (voice), played by Omid Abtahi.
Steve Trevor (voice), played by Chris Diamantopoulos.
Hourman (voice), played by Matthew Mercer.
Jay Garrick (voice), played by Armen Taylor.
Justice Society: World War II is an American animated
superhero film produced by Warner Bros.
Animation and DC Entertainment.
It is the 44th film of the DC Universe Animated Original Movies, being the second installment
in the DC Animated Movie Universe's second phase, and the seventeenth overall.
The film is directed by Jeff Wamester and starring the
voices of Stana Katic and Matt Bomer.
It tells an original story of the Flash ending up back in time to World War II where he meets the
Justice Society of America and helps them thwart the threat of the Nazis and the Advisor.
The film explores themes of superhero, world war ii,
time travel, based on comic, super power.
The tone is thought_provoking.